hi guys
let's analyze rpg life it's part of the
pharma
group um as you see this is pretty
similar to in doco remedies
right if you saw indoco is also hugging
the 50-day
coming pretty close to the 200 day
so what do we have in terms of
technicals
trend has been established 200 days
rising
50 days rising and if you see
that if you tried doing a breakout trade
you were unsuccessful
because uh although the trend is up
but it's not a very strong trend
it's a bigger trend so if the stock is
in a week trend you've got to buy it
when it's pulling back
when it's coming to the 200-day moving
average
and so on and so forth now
been watching this stock for quite some
time
uh there weren't enough opportunities to
trade because this was trading very
erratic
and i was looking for a good entry point
i've been monitoring this this was the
covet bottom uh the stock
went up 200 percent you know without
taking a breath
with the rising volume which was great
now
i'll show you something interesting here
uh
this correction was an extremely low
volume and the subsequent correction
was also an exceptionally low volume so
when when this happened i was hoping
that the stock sort of consolidates and
breaks out which
did not happen it sort of came down and
then broke down further but
it was contained within this range
right so if you notice
we can that we can safely say that
this stock is pretty much
trading in this range since august last
year
so that that's that's the thing about
this talk it's been trading within
within a 20 which is pretty alright
uh what got me interested now is this
thing went up with good speed with great
volume and it's pulling back now
so now we have an opportunity to buy
this and the interesting thing is that
this correction was also on very low
volume
and then this dip which is happening is
happening on a relatively low volume
as well so what has happened
um obviously stock is below the 21 day
moving average so
it's a shorter moving average you don't
have to worry about it
we're going to be it's it's going to be
a two three month trade
so we'll see what sort of entries can we
make so
i'm buying here close to the 50-day
and it can go down
below the 50-day there are chances that
that may happen
however my stop-loss is going to be
below the 200-day moving average so if
this stocks closes below the 200-day
moving average on a weekly basis
very high volume uh that will be the
trigger for me to get out of this stock
so
i'm buying at these levels even if it
goes below
50 i have a feeling that it goes below
50 and it will quickly
reclaim 50. that that is what happened
here
you know this the trend is up 50 is also
moving upwards
what can also happen now without being
too over confident
what can also happen is that the stock
comes here
and then it goes sideways and then the
50 flattens out
so that can also happen there are three
outcomes to a trade
you buy a stock it can go down
it can go up or it can continue to go
sideways so if it continues to go
sideways we will evaluate it based upon
how it's moving
and then we will take a call
so the downside is is
we've defined the downside and uh
you know we are already in the trade so
but some position i'll be adding more
around these levels
let's look at the fundamentals it's a
small cap company rpg life science
it is into finished dosages and active
api as well
but i think they do most of their
business in india i have not done any
in-depth study on rpg
as such great stuff see promoter is
holding good amount of
shares of something that i really like
you know
uh there are no fis in this but it's a
very small company so if i usually don't
buy into 700 500 crore companies usually
they don't
so you know so that is also one of the
reasons why you'll see
that most of the small really small cap
stocks
they are why are they so erratic they
just can't hold on to their gains they
will go up and then they will quickly
succumb
because you don't have um
patient parties holding the stock public
will just sell the stock if it goes up
10 15
that is essential that is essentially
the problem so you need some uh
fidi participation nevertheless
let's look at the cash flow cash flow
looks pretty good
for a 700 crore company all right
balance sheet there is no loan no
borrowing so that is pretty good
profit and loss so highest profit
since 2010 sales are flat
but they've managed to increase their
margin and
that is doing wonders for them so over a
period of time if you will see since 13
they've done great work they've
increased their margins their margins
have actually become
uh 250 basis points they've risen by
sales have not gone up much sales from
230 crores to 400 crores
but margins have gone up by 250 base
response so that is
good that is good march results
are pretty good you can see here
and these are great set of numbers so
i believe that this talk you'll have to
be patient with this
it's not going to be a 50 mover straight
up overnight and
whenever it goes up it is going to meet
with some amount of
uh selling let's quickly check the
all-time high all-time high is here
see see this stock it goes up but it
quickly meets with selling
like if you if you see the stock goes up
say 200 percent and then
it falls 40 50 so
you have to be for for a breakout trader
see up 150 and then after that it has
fallen
around 25 30 then it
went up say 150
and then it corrected 45 45-50
so then you had another leg
up which was 150
and then it quickly succumbed and fell
so this is the problem with stocks which
in which you don't have institutional
holding it
it will go up very quickly and then it
will just succumb
so you you have to be very quick with
profit booking in these kind of stocks
and
your technical analysis has to be very
strong
need to understand where you know there
is supply coming in in the stock and
how quickly you should exit the stock
so as of now we are buying here
and let's see how it plays out okay
thank you